To establish that our results are statistically significant using
要使用假设检验
hypothesis testing,
确保我们的结果具有统计显著性
you need to calculate how likely it is that your results are due to chance.
你需要计算结果是偶然出现的可能性
In order to calculate this probability, you need to have a hypothesis about what
要计算这个概率 你需要先假设
the results would be if your experiment had no effect.
如果实验没有效果 结果会是怎样
In the Audacity example, we'll collect two samples.
在 Audacity 的例子中 我们采集了两个样本
A control group with the orange button, and
对照组使用橙色按钮
an experimental group with the pink button.
实验组使用粉色按钮
We've already assumed that each group follows a binomial distribution, but
我们之前已经假设过 每个组都遵循二项发布
the probabilities might be different for the two groups.
但是两组的概率可能会不同
I'll call the probability that someone in the control group clicks Pcont for
我将对照组内的点击概率称为 Pcont
control, and the probably that someone in the experiment group clicks Pexp for
将实验组内的点击概率称为
experiment.
Pexp
This potentially gives two different distributions.
这样会导致两种分布
If changing the button color had no effect,
如果变更按钮颜色没有效果
then we would expect the two groups to have equivalent distributions, so
这样两组的分布相同
they would right on top of each other.
双方正好在彼此上方
In other words, p control and p experiment would be equal.
也就是说 Pcont 与 Pexp 相等
Another way of saying this would be that p experiment minus p control equals 0.
另外一种说法也就是 Pexp 减去 Pcont 等于 0
This hypothesis of what our results would look like if the experiment had no
实验无效时我们的结果会是怎样
effect is called the null hypothesis.
这种假设称为零假设
And it is also represented as H naught.
由 Ho 代表
We also need a hypothesis about the results if the experiment does
我们还需要假设如果实验有效
have an effect.
那结果会是怎样
This is called the alternative hypothesis or HA.
这称为备择假设 或 HA
In this case, if changing the button color does have an effect,
在这里 如果变更按钮颜色有效应
we expect the P experiment minus P control is not equal to zero.
那 Pexp 减去 Pcont 不等于 0
Once we've defined these hypotheses, we can estimate p control and
在我们确定这些假设之后 我们可以预估
p experiment from the data we've collected.
采集到的数据中的 P?cont 与 P?exp
Then we'll calculate the difference between these,
然后我们可以计算两者之间的差别
and compute the probability that this difference would have arisen by chance,
以及如果零假设成真
if the null hypothesis were true.
计算这个区别是偶然出现的概率
Then we want to reject the null hypothesis, and conclude that
如果概率非常的小 我们想排除零假设
our experiment has an effect if this probability is small enough.
得出实验有效应的结论
This is the same type of significance threshold as a confidence interval, so
这是与置信区间相同类型的显著性阈值
it make sense to choose the same cutoff.
所以可以选择相同的临界值
Thus, we'll choose the same cutoff as before.
所以我们选择与之前相同的临界值
And reject the null if this probability is less than 0.05.
如果概率小于 0.05 则排除零假设
This cutoff is also called alpha.
临界值也称为 α
Now, suppose you're running an experiment where you have
现在 假设你在运行实验
changed the checkout flow of an online shopping website.
你变更了在线购物网站的付款流程
You test the effectiveness of your change by running an experiment
你想要运行实验测试变更的有效性
where some users check out using the old flow, and some using the new flow.
你让一些用户按照旧流程付款 一些使用新流程
For each group, you measure the proportion, or
测量每一组成功完成付款
the probability who successfully complete the checkout.
的比率或概率
What null and alternative hypothesis would you choose for this experiment?
你会为这个实验选择什么零假设和备择假设？
There could be multiple valid answers, but
可能会有多个有效答案
choose a formulation that you think would work.
选择一个你觉得可行的想法
Share your response in plain English in the forum thread
用通俗易懂的话 将你的回复
linked in the instructor's notes.
分享至讲师注释连接的论坛之中
Then read the response of the person above you in the thread,
阅读论坛中在你之前发布的回复
compare their answer to yours, and leave a comment with your thoughts.
将你的答案与他们进行对比 然后留下你的评论
When you've done this, check this box.
完成这项任务后 勾选这个方框